ADI GONNEN

Full Stack Developer

Cellphone: 054-6768418Address: Ramat Gan

• E-mail: adigonnen@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://adi-gonnen.github.io/portfolio/
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/adi-gonnen

GitHub: https://github.com/adi-gonnen

Junior Full Stack Developer, proficient in JavaScript and Vue.js

Experienced in building complex and responsive single page applications

I have M.Sc. in Biotechnology and Biochemistry and experience of 10 years as a technical leader and project manager in a large international cooperation (Nestle)

I'm highly motivated, have excellent communication skills, fast learner, able to work under pressure, diligent and team player

Education

2018 Full-Stack development bootcamp, Coding-Academy

Excellent practical knowledge at:

JavaScript, ES6, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Vue.JS, Vuex, React, Node.JS, MongoDB

Final project: https://swapandplay.herokuapp.com

2005-2009 M.Sc. at Biochemistry and food industry, the Hebrew University

1999-2003 B.Sc. at Biotechnology Engineering, Ben Gurion University

Skills

Client side: JS, ES6, HTML, CSS, SCSS, AJAX, VUE-JS, React, MVC, Responsive Design

• Server side: Node-JS, MongoDB, REST-API

Experience

2007-2017 Nestle Ice Cream: Senior food technologist and project manager

I managed several projects simultaneously in a short schedule and in collaboration

with other departments. Fluent communication with Nestle abroad.

2006-2007 Tnuva: Food technology and vice quality assurance's manager

Languages

Hebrew-Native

English- Very good

Military Service

1995- 1997 Commander for basic training